[{
	"question": "Which tavern is found in Falador?",
	"answers": {
		"a": "Blue Moon Inn",
		"b": "Pick and Lute",
		"c": "Rising Sun",
		"d": "Poison Arrow"
	},
	"correctAnswer": "c",
	"explanation": "The Blue Moon Inn is found in Varrock, the Pick and Lute in Taverley, and the Poison Arrow in Ardougne."
}, {
	"question": "Which of the following is not a type of mushroom in RuneScape?",
	"answers": {
		"a": "Buttercap",
		"b": "Lactarius",
		"c": "Russula",
		"d": "Chanterelle"
	},
	"correctAnswer": "d",
	"explanation": "Chanterelles are commonly used in cooking in North America and Europe. The other mushrooms are found in-game on various islands in the Arc."
}, {
	"question": "How did wyverns die out?",
	"answers": {
		"a": "Climate change",
		"b": "Disease",
		"c": "Marauding adventurers",
		"d": "Janet Reno"
	},
	"correctAnswer": "a",
	"explanation": "According to the natural history quiz in the Varrock Museum, wyverns became extinct because of climate change."
}, {
	"question": "Which tree in RuneScape is a misspelling of a real-life tree?",
	"answers": {
		"a": "Acadia",
		"b": "Blisterwood",
		"c": "Eucalyptus",
		"d": "Dramen"
	},
	"correctAnswer": "a",
	"explanation": "Acadia is an accidental misspelling of the acacia tree; the developers decided to keep it because they liked it better."
}, {
	"question": "During which quest does Sigmund tie Zanik to the tracks of the Dorgesh-Kaanâ€“Keldagrim train system?",
	"answers": {
		"a": "Another Slice of H.A.M.",
		"b": "Death to the Dorgeshuun",
		"c": "Land of the Goblins",
		"d": "The Chosen Commander"
	},
	"correctAnswer": "a"
}, {
	"question": "Who founded the Moon Clan?",
	"answers": {
		"a": "Pauline Polaris",
		"b": "The Oneiromancer",
		"c": "Janet Reno",
		"d": "V"
	},
	"correctAnswer": "c",
	"explanation": "Janet Reno was an American lawyer who served as the Attorney General of the United States from 1993 until 2001 under Bill Clinton."
}, {
	"question": "Which herb is the primary ingredient in creating Runecrafting potions?",
	"answers": {
		"a": "Clean spirit weed",
		"b": "Clean kwuarm",
		"c": "Clean wergali",
		"d": "Clean bloodweed"
	},
	"correctAnswer": "c",
	"explanation": "The Runecrafting potion, one of the most useless items in the game, is made by combining clean wergali and sheep's wool from a player-owned farm."
}, {
	"question": "Which spell was used to summon Zamorak during Evil Dave's Big Day Out?",
	"answers": {
		"a": "Um nahi listic durooo-rah",
		"b": "Carlem Aber Camerinthum Purchai Gabindo",
		"c": "Dominoes Ad Nauseum, Romanes Eunt Domus",
		"d": "Ika tha nke rius Zanka Tdaterius"
	},
	"correctAnswer": "b",
	"explanation": "The same spell was previously used in the Demon Slayer quest, before it was reworked in 2013, to banish the demon Delrith (albeit with the words in random order)."
}, {
	"question": "The God Wars Dungeon, frozen for thousands of years, was thawed in the Fifth Age. Who rediscovered the temple and its combatants?",
	"answers": {
		"a": "The Temple Knights",
		"b": "The White Knights",
		"c": "Orlando Smith",
		"d": "Drunken Dwarf"
	},
	"correctAnswer": "d",
	"explanation": "A letter written by Sir Gerry, who lies dying outside the entrance to the God Wars Dungeon, describes his efforts to \"investigate the dwarf's drunken claims\"."
}, {
	"question": "Of the four following cities, which one is furthest south?",
	"answers": {
		"a": "Yanille",
		"b": "Al Kharid",
		"c": "Brimhaven",
		"d": "Lletya"
	},
	"correctAnswer": "a"
}]